joytunes.com 2019-10-22

# Privacy Policy | JoyTunes

JoyTunes provides music learning and practice tools for all ages which are fun, challenging and exciting. Here at JoyTunes we are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. 

WE DO NOT SELL OR PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES. 

We value your personal information and are aware to the importance of protecting it. **We are sensitive to your privacy and therefore only collect MINIMAL personal information required for giving you optimal experience**. Be assured that your personal information will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note that your use of our Services is also subject to the Terms of Use. 

**Accessing some parts and features of the Services shall require you to provide a valid e-mail address. We will use your e-mail to send you messages, send you communications about your account or about features in our Services, including periodic updates, other information and offers.**

This Privacy Policy describes: 

  * The information we collect;
  * Purposes for collecting information;
  * How we use the information;
  * How to update your information;
  * Controlling your personal information;
  * Securing your information.

We require that you read this Privacy Policy and encourage you to raise any questions with us. JoyTunes may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective as of September 07, 2015. 

## Collected Information

Some features of the Services do not require any personal information to be submitted. In order to use other features and fully access all of what our Services have to offer you will be required to provide personal information. If you are under 13 you are forbidden to disclose any personal information without appropriate parental or legal guardian approval. 

We collect information mainly for (but not limited to) the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping and statistical analysis;
  * Improving products and services;
  * Keeping in touch with our customers;
  * Improving marketing and promotional efforts.

Collected information may include (without limitation) the following: 

  * Name and role (parent, student, teacher etc.);
  * Contact information including email address and phone number;
  * Demographic information;
  * Information regarding usage of the Services;
  * Sample audio recordings for quality assurance and improving acoustic recognition experience;
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or commercial offers.

## What we do with collected information

We use collected information to better understand your needs and to improve Services offered to you and in particular for (but not limited to) the following reasons: 

  * Improving our Services by identifying your needs;
  * Sending updates about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the e-mail address which you have provided;
  * Monitor the effectiveness of our content;
  * Usage Statistics;
  * Understand user preferences;
  * Improve our promotional activity;
  * Create new services and features.

## Security

We have taken measures to keep our Services secured, and we are committed to ensuring that all of your collected information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We ask that minors check with their parents or guardians before supplying any personal information, however minimal, which may be required to use our Services. We ask that you keep login information to our Services a secret, do not share it with third parties and keep it in a secure place. If you suspect your login information has been compromised you should notify us immediately at info@joytunes.com and change your password. 

From time to time, we review our security mechanisms. Be aware though that, despite the efforts and resources we are investing, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which is placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used and they cannot be used as identifiable information by their own. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer, mobile device or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of some Services. 

## Links to other websites

Our Website (Joytunes.com) may contain links to third party websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to our Services and information we collect. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the Privacy Policy applicable to the website in question. 

## Facebook Connect

Some of our Services include registration via Facebook Connect. Using this functionality is at your sole discretion. When you use Facebook Connect information available about you may be shared with us. You also share your information with Facebook and its Privacy Policy applies to their collection, use, and disclosure of such information. In addition, Facebook may be able to collect information about you. For more information about Facebook Connect, please [click here](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260/). Please note that Facebook’s Privacy Policy is likely to be different from ours and we encourage you to read it. 

## Data Analysis Services 

We may use services such as (but not limited to) Google Analytics to understand users behavior. These tools may use cookies to collect information. We use this information only to manage and improve our Services. 

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the use of your personal information. Whenever you are asked to fill in a form, click the checkbox to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes. You may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@joytunes.com](mailto:info@joytunes.com). 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please e-mail us as soon as possible, at info@joytunes.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

## Disclosing Information

JoyTunes doesn’t share personal identifiable information with third parties. However we may disclose information for the following reasons: (a) if we are required to do so by law; (b) if we are required to do so in a legal process; (c) if we feel that disclosing information might prevent a crime; (d) in order to protect the rights or property of JoyTunes including enforcing the Terms of Use. JoyTunes may employ third parties to perform services for the Site, such as database management, maintenance, marketing, data processing and analytics. These third parties have access to your information only to carry out these tasks on our behalf. 

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition or change of control. 

## QUESTIONS

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to [info@joytunes.com](mailto:info@joytunes.com).
